icici pro heart and cancer protect is a
specially designed health insurance plan
that covers both heart diseases and
cancer on the first diagnosis of a heart
disease or cancer the plan pays your
claim amount up front and what's more
you can get a large cover of rupees 17.8
lakhs for a premium amount of just a
piece hundred per month
here's how the plan works mr kumar buys
the plan at the age of 30 with a cancer
cover of rupees 40 lakhs and a hard
cover of rupees 20 lakhs for a policy
term of 15 years and he pays his
premiums regularly
at age 40 he gets diagnosed with a minor
condition covered by the plan
he immediately receives his claim amount
for further treatment also the company
waves off all future premiums and the
plan continues
unfortunately his illness progresses to
a major condition he then receives the
remaining cover mentioned in his plan
with this money in hand he is able to
get the best treatment and makes a
speedy recovery so take a step today to
protect yourself and your family against
heart diseases and cancer
secure yourself with icici prudential
heart and cancer protect